Register of the Robert Charles Hill papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Political Years File I, 1959-1969
  - Correspondence, 1960-1966
    - Venable, Sammie, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 111: 57)
    - Vereide, Abraham, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 111: 58)
    - Verner, Eyvind, 1961 (Box-folder 111: 59)
    - Wadmond, Lowell, 1965 (Box-folder 111: 60)
    - Wahl, C. H., 1961 (Box-folder 111: 61)
    - Wakefield, Joane, 1962 (Box-folder 111: 62)
    - Waldo, Thayer, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 111: 63)
    - Walker, Robert P., 1961 (Box-folder 111: 64)
    - Wallace, Edith B., 1962 (Box-folder 111: 65)
    - Wallach, Philip C., 1961 (Box-folder 111: 66)
    - Walsh, Joseph C., 1963 (Box-folder 111: 67)
    - Walsh, Larry, 1961 (Box-folder 111: 68)
    - Ward, R. E., Jr., 1964 (Box-folder 111: 69)
    - Waring, Lloyd, 1964 (Box-folder 111: 70)
    - Warner, Selma Warlick, 1961 (Box-folder 111: 71)
    - Warren, Irwin D., 1964 (Box-folder 111: 72)
    - Warwick Hotel (New York City), 1963 (Box-folder 111: 73)
    - Washington Hilton (Washington, D.C.), 1966 (Box-folder 111: 74)
    - Washington Post, 1961 (Box-folder 111: 75)
    - Webb, William J., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 111: 76)
    - Webb School of California, 1964 (Box-folder 111: 77)
    - Weber, Dave, 1961 (Box-folder 111: 78)
    - Weber, William A., 1963-1965 (Box-folder 111: 79)
    - Weeks, John W., 1964 (Box-folder 111: 80)
    - Weeks, Sinclair, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 111: 81)
    - Weeks, Sumner C., 1961 (Box-folder 111: 82)
    - Welch, Robert, 1963 (Box-folder 111: 83)
    - Welch, Rolland, 1961 (Box-folder 111: 84)
    - Wellings, J. H., 1962 (Box-folder 111: 85)
    - Wentworth, Mrs. Allan, 1965 (Box-folder 111: 86)
    - Wentworth, Chapman, 1961 (Box-folder 111: 87)
    - West, Herbert F., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 112: 1)
    - West, John, 1965 (Box-folder 112: 2)
    - West, Linda, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 112: 3)
    - Westhall, Jim, 1962 (Box-folder 112: 4)
    - Weston, William H., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 112: 5)
    - Westphal, Fred, 1962 (Box-folder 112: 6)
    - Wetmore, Rae, 1961 (Box-folder 112: 7)
    - Weyl, Nathaniel, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 112: 8)
    - Wheeler, G. S., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 112: 9)
    - Wheeler, Richard C., 1964 (Box-folder 112: 10)
    - Wheeler, Sarah C., 1962-1963 (Box-folder 112: 11)
    - Wheeler, Walter H., Jr., 1962 (Box-folder 112: 12)
    - Whelan, Thomas E., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 112: 13)
    - Wherland, Doris M., 1962-1965 (Box-folder 112: 14)
    - Whitcomb, Henry F., Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 15)
    - White, Charles M., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 16)
    - White, Jack, 1961 (Box-folder 112: 17)
    - White, Louise, 1961 (Box-folder 112: 18)
    - White, William S., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 19)
    - White Mountain Community Services, 1965 (Box-folder 112: 20)
    - Whitely, J. T., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 21)
    - Whitlock, Emmett, 1961 (Box-folder 112: 22)
    - Whitman, Edmund S., 1961-1963 (Box-folder 112: 23)
    - Whitney, Herbert L., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 24)
    - Whitney, John Hay, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 112: 25)
    - Whitney, Joseph C., 1962 (Box-folder 112: 26)
    - Whittemore, C., 1962 (Box-folder 112: 27)
    - Whittinghill, George, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 112: 28)
    - Wiggin, Chester M., Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 29)
    - Wilder, Joseph R., 1965 (Box-folder 112: 30)
    - Wilhelm, John, 1962 (Box-folder 112: 31)
    - Wilhelm, Marion, 1961 (Box-folder 112: 32)
    - Wilhide, C. R., 1962 (Box-folder 112: 33)
    - Wilkinson, Lee, 1961 (Box-folder 112: 34)
    - Willauer, Whiting, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 112: 35)
    - Williams, Beatrice Page, 1965 (Box-folder 112: 36)
    - Williams, Harrison, 1962 (Box-folder 112: 37)
    - Williams, Murat Willis, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 112: 38)
    - Williams, Theodore S., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 39)
    - Williams, Walter, 1964 (Box-folder 112: 40)
    - Williams, Wash B., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 112: 41)
    - Williamson, Stanley H., 1962 (Box-folder 112: 42)
    - Willits, Joseph H., 1962-1963 (Box-folder 112: 43)
    - Wilson, Charles W. S., Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 44)
    - Wilson, Edith Dulles, 1965 (Box-folder 112: 45)
    - Wilson, J., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 46)
    - Wilson, John P., 1962-1965 (Box-folder 112: 47)
    - Wintersteen, Prescott, 1961 (Box-folder 112: 48)
    - Wise, Watson W., 1960-1961 (Box-folder 112: 49)
    - Withey, Francis, 1964 (Box-folder 112: 50)
    - Wood, Paul F., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 51)
    - Wood, Robert, 1963 (Box-folder 112: 52)
    - Wood, Virginia C., 1962 (Box-folder 112: 53)
    - Woodbridge, Henry S., 1963-1964 (Box-folder 112: 54)
    - Woods, Rose Mary, 1965 (Box-folder 112: 55)
    - Woodward, Robert F., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 112: 56)
    - Woodward, Warren G., 1964 (Box-folder 112: 57)
    - Works, David A., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 58)
    - Wozencraft, Frank W., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 59)
    - Wright, Harry, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 112: 60)
    - Wright, S. Bolling, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 112: 61)
    - Wright, William Diggs, 1961 (Box-folder 112: 62)
    - Wrightson, George D., Jr., 1962 (Box-folder 112: 63)
    - Wygant, Michael G., 1964 (Box-folder 112: 64)
    - Wyman, Louis C., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 112: 65)
    - Young, Sharlene, 1962 (Box-folder 112: 66)
    - Zalamea, Luis, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 112: 67)
    - Zapata, Roberto, Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 112: 68)
    - Zuleta Angel, Eduardo, 1963 (Box-folder 112: 69)
    - Zwart, Martin, 1961 (Box-folder 112: 70)
  - Interview transcript, undated (Box-folder 112: 71)
  - Miscellany. Invitations, calling cards, notices, announcements, programs, notes, writings, and printed matter, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 113: 1)
  - Speech file, 1961-1968
    - Clippings, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 113: 2)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1966
      - 1961 (Box-folder 113: 3-6)
      - 1962 (Box-folder 114: 1-2)
      - 1963 (Box-folder 114: 3-4)
      - 1964 (Box-folder 114: 5)
      - 1965 (Box-folder 114: 6)
      - 1966 (Box-folder 114: 7)
    - Memoranda and notes, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 114: 8)
    - Newsletters, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 114: 9)
    - Printed matter, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 115: 1)
    - Speeches by Robert C. Hill, 1961-1968
      - Holographs, undated (Box-folder 115: 2)
      - Notes, undated (Box-folder 115: 3-4)
      - Press releases, 1962 (Box-folder 115: 5)
      - Printed copies, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 115: 6)
      - Typescripts, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 115: 7-8)
    - Speeches by others, 1949-1968 (Box-folder 115: 9)
    - Speeches by others, 1949-1968 (Box-folder 116: 1-2)
    - Writings, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 116: 3)
    - Speech regrets file. Correspondence, 1961-1966
      - 1961 (Box-folder 116: 4)
      - 1962 (Box-folder 116: 5)
      - 1963 (Box-folder 116: 6)
      - 1964 (Box-folder 116: 7)
      - 1965 (Box-folder 116: 8)
      - 1966 (Box-folder 116: 9)
  - Subject file, 1959-1969
    - Alliance for Progress. Clippings, and press release, 1966 (Box-folder 116: 10)
    - American Institute for Free Labor Development. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, agenda, newsletters, and printed matter, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 116: 11)
    - American Institute for Free Labor Development. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, agenda, newsletters, and printed matter, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 117: 1)
    - American Society of International Law. Brochures, and letters, 1960 (Box-folder 117: 2)
    - Americas Foundation. Correspondence, minutes, memoranda, and lists, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 117: 3)
    - Battin, James F. Letter, clipping, and notice, 1963 (Box-folder 117: 4)
    - Bracero program. Correspondence, notes, clippings, and brochure, 1965 (Box-folder 117: 5)
    - Business Council for International Understanding. Note, brochures, and memoranda, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 117: 6)
    - Canadian International Power Company. Correspondence, reports, memoranda, resolutions, agenda, and printed matter, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 117: 7-9)
    - Canadian Interational Power Company. Correspondence, reports, memoranda, resolutions, agenda, and printed matter, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 118: 1)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions. Report, brochure, and letter, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 118: 2)
    - Central America. Correspondence, and memorandum, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 118: 3)
    - China. Pamphlet, leaflet, and serial issue, 1966 (Box-folder 118: 4)
    - Clubs. Correspondence, and miscellanea, 1960-1966
      - Chevy Chase Club, Chevy Chase, Md., 1962 (Box-folder 118: 5)
      - Country Club, Brookline, Mass., 1960 (Box-folder 118: 6)
      - Elks Club, Littleton, N. H., 1960 (Box-folder 118: 7)
      - Metropolitan Club, Washington, D.C., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 118: 8)
      - Miscellany, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 118: 9)
    - Communism. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, notes, clippings, testimony, and brochure, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 118: 10)
    - Consumer project. Correspondence, memoranda, clippings, and draft legislation, 1964 (Box-folder 118: 11)
    - Darlington Manufacturing Company case. Correspondence, memoranda, and statement, 1964 (Box-folder 118: 12)
    - Decoration - Peruvian Grand Cross of Merit. Correspondence, and clippings, 1961 (Box-folder 118: 13)
    - Deering Milliken Company. Correspondence, memoranda, notes, clippings, press releases, and draft legislation, 1964 (Box-folder 118: 14)
    - Election to New Hampshire state Legislature. Letters of congratulation, 1960 (Box-folder 118: 15)
    - Europe, Visit to, Correspondence, schedules, and miscellany, 1963. 1963 (Box-folder 118: 16)
    - Free Cuba News. Issues, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 118: 17)
    - Freedom Academy (Proposed) Correspondence, and clippings, 1965 (Box-folder 118: 18)
    - Government publications. Correspondence, and miscellany, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 118: 19)
    - Governor's Expanded Air Service Committee (New Hampshire) Memorandum, 1964 (Box-folder 118: 20)
    - Hanson's Latin American Letter. Issues, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 118: 21)
    - Hibler, Bernard C. Deposition, 1963 (Box-folder 119: 1)
    - Hillwood Corporation. Correspondence, memoranda, notes, minutes, and printed matter, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 119: 2-4)
    - Honduras - Presidential inauguration, Program, 1965. 1965 (Box-folder 119: 5)
    - Intelligence Digest. Article, 1963 (Box-folder 119: 6)
    - International Meeting of Financial Institutions for Development, Caracas, Correspondence, program, brochures, and miscellany, 1964. 1964 (Box-folder 119: 7)
    - International Power Company. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, resolutions, agenda, and printed matter, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 119: 8-9)
    - Interser. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, and brochures, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 119: 10)
    - Interser. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, and brochures, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 120: 1)
    - Latin America, Visit to, Correspondence, reports, and notes, 1963. 1963 (Box-folder 120: 2)
    - Latin American Free Trade Association. Report, undated (Box-folder 120: 3)
    - Life Magazine book on Mexico, Introduction to. Drafts, galleys, and correspondence, 1961 (Box-folder 120: 4)
    - Littleton, N. H. - Town manager plan. Correspondence, memoranda, and miscellany, 1961 (Box-folder 120: 5)
    - Meany, George. Memorandum, 1962 (Box-folder 120: 6)
    - Merck and Company. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, agenda, minutes, statements, and printed matter, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 120: 7-9)
    - Merck and Company. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, agenda, minutes, statements, and printed matter, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 121: 1-4)
    - Merck and Company. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, agenda, minutes, statements, and printed matter, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 122: 1-3)
    - Mexican Academy of International Law. Correspondence, clippings, and speech, 1960 (Box-folder 122: 4)
    - Mexican Chamber of Commerce of the U.S. Correspondence, minutes, bulletins, and miscellany, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 122: 5-6)
    - Mexico. Memoranda, notes, prospectuses, and speech, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 123: 1)
    - Monterey Railway, Light and Power Company. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, agenda, and minutes, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 123: 2)
    - National Council of Churches. Clippings, bulletins, pamphlet, leaflets, report, press release, and memoranda, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 123: 3)
    - National Legislative Conference. Report, 1961 (Box-folder 123: 4)
    - National school lunch program. Letters, leaflets, brochures, bulletins, and statutes, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 123: 5)
    - Nation's Security. Issue, 1963 (Box-folder 123: 6)
    - New Hampshire
      - House of Representatives. Correspondence, and statements, 1961 (Box-folder 123: 7)
      - Legislation. Correspondence, memoranda, notes, reports, draft legislation, and printed matter, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 123: 8)
      - Politics and government. Correspondence, memoranda, notes, reports, clippings, serial issues, and printed matter, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 123: 9-10)
      - Primary election, Clippings, 1964. 1964 (Box-folder 123: 11)
    - Nixon, Richard M.
      - campaign trip. Itineraries, notes, press releases, speech, menus, and clipping, 1964 1964 (Box-folder 124: 1)
      - campaign, 1968
        - Campaign contributions. Correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 2)
        - Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 124: 3)
        - Correspondence, 1967-1969
          - Adams, John Kay, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 4)
          - Agather, Victor N., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 5)
          - Alexander, Elwood R., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 6)
          - Allen, Richard V., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 7)
          - Asher, Robert E., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 8)
          - Astor, Mrs. Vincent, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 9)
          - Baker, Howard H., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 10)
          - Bayley, Arnold, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 11)
          - Behavior Systems, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 12)
          - Bermudez, Antonio J., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 13)
          - Bethune, Philip H., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 14)
          - Bishop, Max W., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 15)
          - Braggiotti, D. Chadwick, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 16)
          - Butler, Marion, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 17)
          - Castro, Raul H., 1969 (Box-folder 124: 18)
          - Cavan, W. E., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 19)
          - Chennault, Anna, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 20)
          - Clark, Roger A., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 21)
          - Crane, Kent B., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 22)
          - Crowe, Philip Kingsland, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 124: 23)
          - Davenport, Eldon A., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 24)
          - Diaz, Jose Gregorio, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 25)
          - Dirksen, Everett McKinley, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 26)
          - Ellsworth, Robert, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 27)
          - Evans, Thomas W., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 28)
          - Flemming, Harry S., 1969 (Box-folder 124: 29)
          - Forsten, Weikko A., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 30)
          - Garcia de Alba, Pablo M., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 31)
          - Goodrich, Burnell N., 1969 (Box-folder 124: 32)
          - Goodsell, Mr., undated (Box-folder 124: 33)
          - Gray, Cecil W., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 34)
          - Greenfield, Jeffrey, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 35)
          - Guest, Winston F. C., 1969 (Box-folder 124: 36)
          - Hanes, John W., Jr., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 37)
          - Hillings, Pat, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 38)
          - Hitt, Pat, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 39)
          - Hoover, John P., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 40)
          - Hotchkis, Preston, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 41)
          - Katzen, Bernard, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 42)
          - Kern, Harry F., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 43)
          - Kleindienst, Richard G., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 44)
          - Kluckhohn, Frank L., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 45)
          - Knudsen, C. Calvert, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 46)
          - Leddy, Raymond G., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 47)
          - Lodge, John Davis, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 48)
          - Loeb, William, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 49)
          - Love, Charles B., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 50)
          - McCuen, John J., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 51)
          - McGuire, Perkins, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 52)
          - McIntosh, Dempster, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 53)
          - Mack, James E., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 54)
          - Macomber, William B., Jr., 1969 (Box-folder 124: 55)
          - Marquez Sterling, Carlos, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 56)
          - Martin, John B., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 57)
          - Meyerhoff, Arthur E., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 58)
          - Mitchell, John, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 59)
          - Monroe, Michael C., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 60)
          - Morris, Robert, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 61)
          - Munson, Lyle H., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 62)
          - Nixon, Richard M., 1968-1969 (Box-folder 124: 63)
          - Nolting, Frederick E., Jr., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 64)
          - Nyaradi, Nicholas, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 65)
          - O'Connor, Roderic L., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 66)
          - Olds, Glenn A., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 67)
          - Orleans, Fred A., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 68)
          - Pappagianis, George S., 1967 (Box-folder 124: 69)
          - Penney, Annette Culler, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 70)
          - Rebozo, C. G., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 71)
          - Rhyne, Charles S., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 72)
          - Rowe, David N., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 73)
          - Smith, Gerard C., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 74)
          - Smith, Laurence C., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 75)
          - Stans, Maurice H., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 76)
          - Sterling, David A., 1967 (Box-folder 124: 77)
          - Stimpson, Harry F., Jr., 1968 (Box-folder 124: 78)
          - Strand, William, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 79)
          - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, 1968 (Box-folder 124: 80)
          - Tas, Sol, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 1)
          - Teague, Charles M., 1968 (Box-folder 125: 2)
          - Teller, Edward, 1969 (Box-folder 125: 3)
          - Telles, Raymond, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 4)
          - Theberge, James D., 1968 (Box-folder 125: 5)
          - Tobin, Edmund P., 1968 (Box-folder 125: 6)
          - Todd, Carlos, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 7)
          - Tower, John G., 1968-1969 (Box-folder 125: 8)
          - Trudeau, Arthur G., 1968 (Box-folder 125: 9)
          - Trudeau, Pierre Elliott, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 10)
          - Turkel, Harry Raymond, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 11)
          - Unidentified, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 12)
          - Upston, John E., 1968 (Box-folder 125: 13)
          - Washburn, Abbott, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 14)
          - Webb, William J., 1968 (Box-folder 125: 15)
          - Weyl, Nathaniel, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 16)
          - Whitaker, John C., 1968 (Box-folder 125: 17)
          - Williams, John J., 1968 (Box-folder 125: 18)
          - Williams, W. Walter, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 19)
          - Withey, Francis M., 1969 (Box-folder 125: 20)
          - Woodbridge, Henry S., 1968 (Box-folder 125: 21)
          - Woods, Rose Mary, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 125: 22)
          - Wright, Harry, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 23)
          - Wyman, Louis C., 1968 (Box-folder 125: 24)
          - Zuniga, Ricardo, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 25)
        - Finance Committee. Correspondence, reports, and memoranda, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 125: 26)
        - Job requests. Correspondence, and resumes, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 125: 27-28)
        - Key Issues Committee. Correspondence, notes, memoranda, and report, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 29)
        - Memoranda, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 125: 30-31)
        - Miscellany. Notes, lists, invitations, printed matter, and charts, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 125: 32)
        - Press releases, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 125: 33)
        - Speeches, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 125: 34)
        - Women for Nixon. Correspondence, lists, and clippings, 1968 (Box-folder 125: 35)
    - Pan American Headlines. Issue, 1963 (Box-folder 126: 1)
    - Panama Canal. Letter, and printed matter, 1964 (Box-folder 126: 2)
    - Pension Corporation of America. Correspondence, memoranda, notes, clippings and miscellany, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 126: 3)
    - Project Showboat. Correspondence, and prospectus, 1966 (Box-folder 126: 4)
    - Republican Associates of Los Angeles County. Handbooks, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 126: 5)
    - Republican Congressional Committee Newsletter. Issues, 1963 (Box-folder 126: 6)
    - Republican Coordinating Committee. Task Force on the Conduct of Foreign Relations
      - Clippings, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 126: 7)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1966
        - Allott, Gordon, 1965 (Box-folder 126: 8)
        - Babcock, Tim, 1965 (Box-folder 126: 9)
        - Bass, Perkins, 1965 (Box-folder 126: 10)
        - Bliss, Ray C., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 126: 11)
        - Bolton, Frances P., 1966 (Box-folder 126: 12)
        - Bovaird, Rose, 1965 (Box-folder 126: 13)
        - Burke, Arleigh, 1965 (Box-folder 126: 14)
        - Clarke, Biehl P., 1965 (Box-folder 126: 15)
        - Clay, Lucius D., 1965 (Box-folder 126: 16)
        - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1966 (Box-folder 126: 17)
        - Eisenhower, Milton S., 1965 (Box-folder 126: 18)
        - Findley, Paul, 1966 (Box-folder 126: 19)
        - Frelinghuysen, Peter H. B., 1966 (Box-folder 126: 20)
        - Gadsden, Henry W., 1965 (Box-folder 126: 21)
        - Hickenlooper, Bourke B., 1966 (Box-folder 126: 22)
        - Hughes, Margaret J., 1966 (Box-folder 126: 23)
        - Isaacson, John T., 1965 (Box-folder 126: 24)
        - Javits, Jacob K., 1966 (Box-folder 126: 25)
        - Judd, Walter H., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 126: 26)
        - Laird, Melvin R., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 126: 27)
        - Leymeister, Ronald L., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 126: 28)
        - Lodge, John Davis, 1966 (Box-folder 126: 29)
        - McCormick, Robert L. L., 1966 (Box-folder 126: 30)
        - Niemeyer, Gerhart, 1966 (Box-folder 126: 31)
        - Nofziger, Lyn, 1965 (Box-folder 126: 32)
        - Nunez, Julio, 1965 (Box-folder 126: 33)
        - Nyaradi, Nicholas, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 126: 34)
        - Peterson, Arthur L., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 126: 35)
        - Prendergast, William B., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 126: 36)
        - Robertson, Walter S., 1966 (Box-folder 126: 37)
        - Rockefeller, David, 1965 (Box-folder 126: 38)
        - Romney, George, 1966 (Box-folder 126: 39)
        - Rowe, David N., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 126: 40)
        - Saltonstall, Leverett, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 127: 1)
        - Scranton, William W., 1965 (Box-folder 127: 2)
        - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, 1966 (Box-folder 127: 3)
        - Stuckey, John M., 1966 (Box-folder 127: 4)
        - Sunderland, Mr., 1965 (Box-folder 127: 5)
        - Taylor, James, 1966 (Box-folder 127: 6)
        - Woodbridge, Henry S., 1965 (Box-folder 127: 7)
        - Zander, Arnold S., 1966 (Box-folder 127: 8)
      - Draft reports, 1965-1966
        - Alliance for Progress, undated (Box-folder 127: 9)
        - Dominican Republic, undated (Box-folder 127: 10)
        - Economic foreign policy, 1965 (Box-folder 127: 11)
        - Foreign policy, 1966 (Box-folder 127: 12)
        - Latin America, 1965 (Box-folder 127: 13-14)
        - Merchant Marine, 1965 (Box-folder 127: 15)
        - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1966 (Box-folder 127: 16)
        - United Nations, 1966 (Box-folder 127: 17)
        - Vietnam, 1965 (Box-folder 127: 18)
      - Memoranda, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 127: 19)
      - Miscellany. Notes, lists, agenda, and minutes, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 127: 20)
      - Press Releases, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 127: 21)
      - Printed matter, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 128: 1)
      - Writings, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 128: 2)
    - Republican National Committee. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, lists, bulletins, and pamphlet, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 128: 3)
    - Revere Sugar Refinery. Correspondence, memoranda, lists, notes, bulletins, clippings, and speeches, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 128: 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. Letter, press release, leaflet, and clippings, 1963 (Box-folder 128: 5)